I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
（泉(いずみ)）キャッ
（コユキ）うわ…
into the world of perfect free
（コユキ）
俺たちが たどりついたのは—
(You ain't no lonely!)
１軒の古ぼけた釣堀だった
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
（コユキ）凶暴だから気をつけて！
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
あ…
（泉）おいで！
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
キャッ！ もう…
I was made to hit in America
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
We ended up at an old house
with a fishing hole.
He's vicious! Watch out!
C'mere!
私 犬 飼ってたから
I used to have a dog.
すごいよ 泉ちゃん
You're amazing, Izumi-chan.
えーと…
Hmm...
まず グーで においをかがせます
First, you let him sniff your fist.
それで犬に覚えさせてから
ゆっくり なでてあげれば…
And when the dog knows your scent,
you stroke it very gently.
ウフフッ ほらね！
You see?
うん！ えー まず…
グーで においをかがせて—
'Kay.
First, you let him sniff your fist...
and then stroke his head...
頭を… なでて…
（コユキ）うあっ！ いててて…
いってぇ！ うう…
（竜介(りゅうすけ)の英語）
Beck! Stop it!
（コユキ）うあっ！ いててて…
いってぇ！ うう…
（竜介）よう！
Yo!
Beck, go play by yourself.
（コユキ）竜介君…
Ryusuke-kun!
ここが… 竜介君の家？
Is this your house, Ryusuke-kun?
ああ 仕事場でもある
Yup. As well as my workplace.
（泉）なんか… 迫力あるねー
It has character.
Sorry, my house is old.
Well...you can use it however you like.
All right.
-See you tomorrow.
-Bye-bye, Grandma. See ya.
（竜介）ここさぁ…
何か 居心地いいんだよな
This place is really comfortable.
（コユキ）
ＣＤ… たくさんありますねー
You have so many CDs.
それと…
-And...
-Lots of girls' romances, right?
（竜介）女物のマンガ
すごいだろ？
妹が置いてったのに
ハマっちゃったんだ
My kid sister left 'em,
and I got hooked on them.
（コユキ）少女マンガ…
Young girls' comics?
（竜介）これ 面白いぞ
This one's good.
Christy Sakuishi's "Happy Sangokushi".
クリスティ作石(さくいし)の
「ハッピー三国志」
（コユキ）あ！ それ知ってます
Oh, I know that one!
（泉）これ… わーっ！
Look! Wow!
これって—
This is a Dying Breed CD
from their indie days!
ダイブリがインディーズ時代に
出したＣＤじゃないですか？
（竜介）え？ うん そうだけど…
Huh? Oh yeah...
これって 今すごいプレミア
付いてるんですよー
This one's worth a lot now.
Oh yeah?
（竜介）それ オーストラリアの
バンドのカバーなんだぜ
That cover's from the band, Australia.
（泉）へー！ 聴きたいな～
Wow! I'd love to hear it!
（竜介）オリジナルは
結構カントリーでさ—
The original one was quite country.
Kinda like "Drag Car Boy."
ドラッグ・カウボーイ風なんだ
（泉）あ ドラッグ・カウボーイなら
私も持ってます
Oh, I have "Drag Car Boy."
（竜介）うん エディのヤツ
マニアだからな
Eddie's totally into it.
（コユキ）全然ついていけないや…
I can't follow their conversation at all.
（コユキ）ハァ…
-You than before
（国吉(くによし)ちえみの曲）
Close your eyes, no need to panic
Feel the void, feel the beat,
there's no need to say it
-Tomorrow will surely be wow wow
-Yukio! Telephone!
（コユキの母）幸雄～ 電話よ！
-So cheer up,
because I want to see your smile
-Someone named Minami-san.
南さんだって
（コユキ）南？ 男の人？
-So cheer up,
because I want to see your smile
-Minami? A man?
（コユキの母）アッハハハ…
もしもし… ああ 竜介君！
Hello?
Oh, Ryusuke-kun!
うん ライブ 日曜なんだね
Yeah. Live on Sunday, right?
うん 泉ちゃんにも伝えておくよ
Yup. I'll tell Izumi-chan too.
Uh-huh...Yup.
（竜介）それと お前に１つ
言っておきたいことがある
I also wanna tell you something.
え… 何？
Huh? What is it?
（竜介）お前は14歳 俺は16歳だ
You're 14. And I'm 16 years old.
でもさ 俺のこと… 竜介って呼べよ
So just call me "Ryusuke".
男から“竜介君”なんて
呼ばれるとさ—
When a guy calls me "Ryusuke-kun",
it feels creepy.
気持ちワリィんだ
聞こえてるか？
You listening?
（竜介）おかしいか？
You think it's funny?
日本社会の規則っていうか
風土っていうか…
So it's the Japanese way...
what society expects.
おい お前 聞いてるか？
But are you listening?
I'm just not into
feudalistic practices like that.
そういう封建的なしきたりって
苦手なんだ
Koyuki, did you hear me?
コユキ？ 聞いてるか？
Okay. I'll call you
just Ryusuke from now on.
うん 竜介って…
これから そう呼ぶよ
それじゃ 日曜日に
I'll see you on Sunday.
のわぁっ！
ハァ… ハァ… 遅れてごめん！
Sorry I'm late!
Koyuki-san! What were you
doing at the intersection?
コユキさあ
横断歩道の所で何してたの？
Did you lose something?
何か落とした？ フッ
C'mon, let's go.
さ 行こう！
Ryusuke-kun drew me
this map to the live house.
（コユキ）
これが竜介君が書いてくれた—
ライブハウスの地図なんだ
-All simple hiragana.
-I guess he can't write kanji.
（コユキ）ひらがな…
漢字 苦手みたい
Say, Izumi-chan.
（コユキ）ねぇ 泉ちゃん
Hmm? What is it?
（泉）ん… 何？
Why don't you start seeing Ryusuke-kun?
（コユキ）竜介君と つきあえば？
I mean, he's cool...
だって…
竜介君ってカッコいいしさ
Oh, right! I want you to
listen to something, Koyuki!
あ そうだ！
コユキに聴かせたいものがあるの
Here it is.
あった あった… はい
This.
This is Dying Breed.
これが ダイイング・ブリード
What's the matter?
どうした？
This is...
（コユキ）これ…
Oh, sorry! The battery's dead!
（泉）あ ごめん！ 電池切れてるね
Izumi-chan!
（カヨ）泉ちゃ～んっ！
Oh, Kayo-chan! You're late!
あっ カヨちゃん 遅いぞー！
Sorry, sorry!
（カヨ）ワリィ ワリィ
Dying...Breed.
ダイイング… ブリード…
Koyuki, hurry it up!
コユキー 早くー！
We'll leave you behind!
（カヨ）置いてっちゃうぞー
This way.
（泉）こっち こっち
Hey!
（カヨ）おーい
This is...an interesting place.
（コユキ）面白い… とこだね
-Oh, there's a good crowd.
-Yeah.
（カヨ）おー 集まってるじゃん
（コユキ・泉）うん
These are tonight's bands.
（カヨ）
これが きょうの出演バンドだよ
（コユキ・泉）ふーん…
What's wrong, Koyuki?
（泉）どうしたの コユキ？
A live house...
（コユキ）ライブハウス…
Wait! That's-!
（泉）あっ そっちは…
Cut the crap!
（栄二(えいじ)）ふざけるな！
Can't you listen to me?!
俺の言うことが聞けないのか！
The entire band agreed to it.
（栄二）バンドみんなの考えだ
I like my black hair.
俺は自分の黒い髪が好きなんだ
Hey, thanks for coming.
ああ よく来たな
Err...Umm...
（コユキ）あ… いや…
Ryusuke...
竜介…
If you expect to be a pro,
you'd better listen to me.
お前もプロとして
やっていくつもりなら—
俺の言うことを聞け！
フッ… この前の白い衣装
サイアクだったぜ
That white outfit
the other time was the pits.
-Stop it!
-That's enough!
（ボーカル）やめろよ！
いいかげんにしろ！
There's a scout in the audience tonight!
きょうは事務所の人が
見に来てるんだぞ
With any luck, we can quit our
part-time jobs and focus on our music!
（東郷(とうごう)）俺たち
うまくいきゃ バイトやめて—
（竜介）離せよ！
音楽に集中できるんだぞ！
-Understand?!
-Eiji!
分かってんのかよ！
（ボーカル）
栄二… 栄二！
-Leggo of me!
-Eiji!
（栄二）離せって！
-Let's go.
-Yeah...
（泉）行こう…
（コユキ）うん
（ボーカル）
頼む！ やめろ！
Stop it!
They were really going at it.
何か すごい迫力
They're all serious about this.
So they get uptight.
（カヨ）みんなマジなんだ
イラついてんのさ
It's 1500 yen, right?
（コユキ）1,500円ですよね
-Plus 500 yen for drinks.
-Here you go.
（受付係）ドリンク代 500円ですー
（コユキ）はい
-All we need is get into the night
-So this is a live concert...
（コユキ）これが… ライブ…
-People need it
-Wow...
-get into the night
-Maho...Minami.
南… 真帆(まほ)
-Let it the funk
-Maho...Minami.
14歳 俺の妹だよ
（コユキ）え？
-Ain't a thing
-14 years old.
-All we need is
-My kid sister.
-Get into the night
Let it the funk
イェイ！
We got to move in the world destruction
-Get in tha funky punky!
-Yeah!
（カヨ）「シリアル・ママ」
Serial Mama.
それが竜介君のいるバンドの名前？
Is that the name of Ryusuke-kun's band?
うん たぶん栄二君が
つけたんじゃないかな
Yeah. Eiji-kun probably picked the name.
シリアル・ママ…
Serial Mama...
栄二君 １年前に—
A year ago, Eiji-kun said he was
gonna make the ultimate band.
最強のバンドをつくるんだ！
って みんなに言ってさ
（コユキ・泉）最強のバンド？
-The "ultimate band"?
竜介君 誘うのも
かなり強引だったそうだよ
Apparently, he really bugged
Ryusuke-kun about joining.
ねえ カヨちゃん
あの人かな？
Say Kayo-chan...Is that him?
ああ 事務所の人ね
Oh yeah, from the production company.
Eiji-kun's friend brought him.
栄二君の知り合いが
連れてきたみたい
うまくいけば メジャーデビューも
夢じゃないかも
If things go well, a major debut
may no longer be just a dream.
-What do you think?
-Looks good.
あの２人 大丈夫かな？
I wonder if those two are okay.
そうなんだよ
I know! It's like they have two leaders,
リーダーが
２人いるみたいでさ
見てても
ハラハラしちゃうんだ
and it's nerve-wracking just watching them.
（男性）大丈夫ったい
（泉）ん？
Don't worry about 'em.
（男性）違う個性が—
Two opposites with perfect techniques
combine to create that sound!
抜群のテクで
共鳴し合(お)っとうサウンド！
あのツインリードギターは
正直 感動もんやけぇ！
Those two lead guitars...
Man, talk about music!
シリアル・ママ…
ばりサイコーったい！
Serial Mama...They are the best!
おっ 始まるよ
Oh, they're up.
もっと前で見よう！
Let's go up closer!
（女性客１）イェーイ！
Yay!
（女性客２）
栄二～！ 愛してる～！
Eiji! I love you!
（男性）イヤッホー！
（コユキ）わぁっ
ヤッホゥ！
Yahoo!
（ボーカル）
シリアル・ママでーす！
We're the Serial Mama!
（ボーカル）あれ おっかしいなー
Hey! That's weird!
すんませーん！
今 直すんで ちょっと待ってねー
Sorry about that!
We'll get it fixed, just a sec!
え～っと この時間使って
告知タ～イム！
Hmm...Let's use this time
for some chit-chat!
んー 栄二
アレ言っちゃっていいのか？
Eiji, can I tell them that?
Boy, that was a shock.
Does this happen often?
ビックリしたぁ
こういうことって
よくあるんですか？
ギターの弦が切れる
なんてーのは まあ—
A guitar string will break sometimes.
よくあるけど—
ここまでひどいのは
めったにないよ
But something this bad never happens.
What a day for it to happen...
しかも きょうは…
（スタッフ１）ギターのライン
Ｃ-１つないでみてくださーい！
Can you connect the guitar line to C1?
（スタッフ２）了解ですー！
Got it!
（竜介）シールドは問題ない
My shield is fine.
（栄二）こっちはダメだ
切れちゃってるぞ
Not mine. It's broken.
（スタッフ１）
はい 他ので代用します！
I'll switch it!
（男性客１）まだかよ！
-How long's it gonna take?!
-Hurry it up!
（女性客３）早くしてー
（男性客２）始めろー！
（女性客４）栄二～！
そっか エフェクターの
ボリュームが下がってたんだ
I got it. The effecter volume was too low.
栄二！
Eiji!
おう！ こっちもオーケーだぜ！
Yo! I'm okay on my side!
（スタッフ１）すみません！
お待たせしました
Thank you for your patience! Let's go!
オーケーです！
You're the best!
（男性客３）
シリアル・ママ サイコー！
おっと？
Huh?
ハァ… ハァ…
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
They're having a wrap party
at a pub up the street.
（泉）この先の居酒屋で
打ち上げあるってさ
-Won't you join us, Koyuki?
-Yeah.
コユキも行かない？
（コユキ）うん…
ねえ 泉ちゃんは耳 平気？
Hey, Izumi-chan, are your ears okay?
（泉）んー？ ハハッ そっか
コユキはライブ初めてだもんね
Oh, that's right. It was your
first time at a live concert.
Don't worry. Your hearing
will return in a bit.
（カヨ）
大丈夫だよ そのうち戻るよ
（コユキ）俺 うちに電話してくる
（泉）じゃあ 先に行ってるね
I'm going to call home.
We'll go on ahead.
"Pub New Shinshu"
-Okay, three orders of chuhai.
-Hey, gimme some beef tongue.
（店員）はーい 酎ハイ３丁！
（客）おねーさん
牛タンちょうだーい
"Pub New Shinshu"
Hey, Eiji-kun and Ryusuke haven't
exchanged a word since the fight.
（カヨ）
ねえねえ 栄二君と竜介—
（店員）はいよー
（カヨ）
ねえねえ 栄二君と竜介—
あれから全然話してないよ～
ヒック…
Hey, Eiji-kun and Ryusuke haven't
exchanged a word since the fight.
Geez...This band is really in trouble.
このバンド マジヤバいかもよー
What are you saying, girl?!
なーんば言いよっとですか～
おねえさん！
The Eiji and Ryusuke duo
will be together forever!
栄二と竜介のコンビは
永遠に不滅ったい！
あ… 俺 トイレ
I'm going to the john.
（カヨ）ヒック… マジヤバい
This is the pits!
（男性）
不滅ったい…
ハァ…
Say, this is the toilet, right?
（真帆）ねえ！
（コユキ）ん…
（真帆）これって トイレだよね？
Oh, you're Ryusuke-kun's younger sister.
あー 竜介君の妹さん！
うん… これってトイレ？
-Is this the toilet?
-Yeah, I think so.
（コユキ）うん そうだと思う
Thanks.
サンキュー
Oh, I see. Maho-chan,
you're not good with kanji either.
（コユキ）そっか 真帆ちゃんも
漢字ダメなんだね エヘヘ…
What?!
Who the fuck are you?!
Idiot.
（真帆）バーカ
Dammit!
（カヨ）ちくしょー！
（男性）
ぬあーっ このアマ～！
-You wench!
-You got Serial Mama all wrong!
（カヨ）
ふざけんじゃねーぞ このヤロー
お前 シリアル・ママって—
10回言ってみろっつうんだよ！
Where's the sake?! Bring the sake!
（カヨ）
酒 持ってこい 酒～！
-Shut up!
-Screw you!
ふざけんなよ お前！
Pankration began in ancient Greece,
（教師）古代ギリシャで発祥した
パンクラチオンが—
and in modern England, it became
popular as the Lancashire style
近代イギリスにおいて—
ランカシャースタイルとして
定着し 現在の—
and was adapted into what
we know today as free-style wrestling.
フリースタイルレスリングに
なったわけだ
And many wrestlers
have come up the ranks
数々の名レスラーを生み出した
ビリー・ライレージム—
after going through
the notorious Snake Pit.
通称スネーク・ピット出身の
レスラーとして—
And famous among them is Karl Gotch.
有名なのは カール・ゴッチ！
-Want to listen to this?
-Can I borrow it?
（泉）これ 聴いてみる？
（コユキ）いいの？ 借りて
もちろん！
Of course!
Ryusuke-kun is really something.
竜介君って すごいよね
Yeah.
I hope you find something
to get passionate about, too.
コユキにも 何か見つかるといいね
Yeah.
You can give it back anytime.
（泉）返すの いつでもいいから
See you!
じゃあ また！
（コユキ）あ… ありがとう！
Thanks!
I think Ishiguro-sempai
may have a thing for you.
（田辺(たなべ)）石黒先輩…
お前のこと 好きなのかも
-I don't think so...
-Neither do I.
そんなこと…
（田辺）ないよなー
Say, Ishiguro. You've been
awfully cheerful lately.
（女子生徒１）なんかさー
最近 石黒 元気だよねぇ
（泉）えー そうかなぁ？
You think so?
（女子生徒２）おっ 怪しいぞー
（泉）ウフッ
I'm suspicious!
It was a mistake. You and me joining up.
失敗だったんだ…
俺とお前が組むこと自体
Yes?
はい… いえ 大丈夫です
No, it's all right.
Yes, I'll be right there!
はい すぐに伺います
はい 失礼します！
Yes, thank you!
It's the weekend,
and I can't even take off!
週末だって休めないんだ
Hard luck.
大変だな
You wouldn't understand
what I have to go through.
お前には 俺の苦労は分かんねえよ
Not you, a CEO's son.
社長の息子のお前には分かんねえよ
Ryusuke...
竜介…
I'm going to form the ultimate band.
俺は… 最強のバンドをつくる
So will I.
俺も つくるよ
Ryusuke-kun...
竜介君…
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Lately, I'm really into the love game!
（千葉(ちば)）
最近 ラブゲームにハマってまーす
"Next Episode"
Lately, I'm really into the love game!
Just kidding.
ウソでーす
"Next Episode"